Jacques Seligmann & Co.
Archives of American Art, Smithsonian Institution
- Correspondence, 1913-1978, Series 1:; (80 linear feet)
  - General Correspondence, 1913-1978, 1.3:
    - Proskauer, Rose & Paskus, 1937-1940 (Box 78, Folder 25)
    - Prouté, Paul (see Paul Prouté, S.A.) (Box 78)
    - Pruyne, Mary, 1933-1939 (Box 78, Folder 26)
    - Public Record Office, London, 1965 (Box 78, Folder 27)
    - Publicity, 1925-1926 (Box 78, Folder 28)
    - Publicity, 1959-1961 (Box 78, Folder 29)
    - Puiforcat, Jean E., 1941-1942 (Box 78, Folder 30)
    - Pulitzer, Joseph, Jr., 1925-1948 (Box 78, Folder 31)
    - Pulitzer, Joseph, Jr., 1949-1968 (Box 78, Folder 32)
    - Putzel, Howard, 1935-1941 (Box 78, Folder 33)
    - Puyvelde, Leo van (see van Puyvelde, Leo) (Box 78)
    - Pyne, Percy B., 1924-1936 (Box 78, Folder 34)
    - Miscellaneous P: Pac-Pao, 1923-1974 (Box 79, Folder 1)
    - Miscellaneous P: Par, 1925-1970 (Box 79, Folder 2)
    - Miscellaneous P: Pas-Pay, 1926-1969 (Box 79, Folder 3)
    - Miscellaneous P: Pea-Pep, 1925-1977 (Box 79, Folder 4)
    - Miscellaneous P: Per-Pew, 1925-1961 (Box 79, Folder 5)
    - Miscellaneous P: Pfa-Pfo, 1926-1949 (Box 79, Folder 6)
    - Miscellaneous P: Pha-Phi, 1923-1968 (Box 79, Folder 7)
    - Miscellaneous P: Pia-Pie, 1924-1968 (Box 79, Folder 8)
    - Miscellaneous P: Pil-Pit, 1935-1968 (Box 79, Folder 9)
    - Miscellaneous P: Pla-Plu, 1924-1962 (Box 79, Folder 10)
    - Miscellaneous P: Poc-Pom, 1923-1964 (Box 79, Folder 11)
    - Miscellaneous P: Pon-Pow, 1924-1977 (Box 79, Folder 12)
    - Miscellaneous P: Pra-Pre, 1924-1968 (Box 79, Folder 13)
    - Miscellaneous P: Pri-Pro, 1925-1959 (Box 79, Folder 14)
    - Miscellaneous P: Pru-Pyn, 1924-1977 (Box 79, Folder 15)
    - Quaritch, Bernard (see Bernard Quaritch, Ltd.) (Box 79)
    - Quatre Chemins-Editart, 1950-1961 (Box 79, Folder 16)
    - Quatre Chemins-Editart, 1962-1976 (Box 79, Folder 17)
    - Queensberry, Lord and Lady, 1927-1931 (Box 79, Folder 18)
    - Quillet, B., 1952-1976 (Box 79, Folder 19)
    - Quinn, Mr. and Mrs. Charles H., 1928-1936 (Box 79, Folder 20)
    - Miscellaneous Q, 1923-1957 (Box 79, Folder 21)
    - R.C.A. Communications, Inc. (see also Radio Corporation of America), 1941-1974 (Box 80, Folder 1)
    - R. L. Polk & Co., Inc., 1923-1950 (Box 80, Folder 2)
    - Rabow, Alexandre & Rose, 1955-1958 (Box 80, Folder 3)
    - Radeke, Eliza G., 1925-1929 (Box 80, Folder 4)
    - Radio Corporation of America (see also R. C. A. Communications, Inc.), 1923 (Box 80, Folder 5)
    - Raeber, Dr. Willi, 1954 (Box 80, Folder 6)
    - Railway Express Agency, 1938-1958 (Box 80, Folder 7)
    - Rains, Samuel G., 1932 (Box 80, Folder 8)
    - Raiss, Carl, 1916-1939 (Box 80, Folder 9)
    - Ramage, Alfred H., 1924-1940 (Box 80, Folder 10)
    - Ramus, Charles F., 1936-1973 (Box 80, Folder 11)
    - Rancheraye & Co. (see De La Rancheraye & Co.) (Box 80)
    - Randahl Shop, 1934-1935 (Box 80, Folder 12)
    - Randall, L. V., 1942-1962 (Box 80, Folder 13)
    - Rasmussen, Mr. and Mrs. George, 1924-1925 (Box 80, Folder 14)
    - Rasmussen, Mr. and Mrs. George, 1926-1927 (Box 80, Folder 15)
    - Rasmussen, Mr. and Mrs. George, 1928-1930 (Box 80, Folder 16)
    - Rasmussen, Mr. and Mrs. George, 1930-1934 (Box 80, Folder 17)
    - Rasmussen, Mr. and Mrs. George, 1935-1936 (Box 80, Folder 18)
    - Rasmussen, Mr. and Mrs. George, 1937-1942 (Box 80, Folder 19)
    - Rasmussen, Henry N., 1946 (Box 80, Folder 20)
    - Ratton, Charles, 1950-1972 (Box 80, Folder 21)
    - Rauch, Nicholas, 1952-1960 (Box 80, Folder 22)
    - Raymond & Raymond, Inc., 1936-1949 (Box 80, Folder 23)
    - Rea, Mrs. Henry R., 1924-1927 (Box 80, Folder 24)
    - Read, Helen Appleton, 1940-1943 (Box 80, Folder 25)
    - Réau, Louis, 1925-1953 (Box 80, Folder 26)
    - Réau, Louis, 1955-1967 (Box 80, Folder 27)
    - Rebay, Hilda (see Solomon R. Guggenheim Foundation, 1941-1953 (Box 80)
    - Reber, Dr. G. F., 1932-1956 (Box 80, Folder 28)
    - Reckford, Mrs. Louis, 1925-1935 (Box 80, Folder 29)
    - Redmond, Roland, 1949-1950 (Box 80, Folder 30)
    - Redon, Arï, 1950-1955 (Box 80, Folder 31)
    - Reed, Mrs. Verner Z., 1925-1936 (Box 80, Folder 32)
    - Reford, Mr. and Mrs. Robert W., 1922-1940 (Box 80, Folder 33)
    - Rehm, T. R., 1950-1951 (Box 80, Folder 34)
    - Reid & Lefèvre, Ltd. (see Alex Reid & Lefèvre, Ltd.) (Box 80)
    - Reinhardt Galleries, 1924-1939 (Box 80, Folder 35)
    - Reinhart, Oskar, 1934-1954 (Box 80, Folder 36)
    - Reiter, Murray, 1965 (Box 80, Folder 37)
    - Remarque, Erich M., 1940-1943 (Box 81, Folder 1)
    - Remington Rand, Inc., 1923-1952 (Box 81, Folder 2)
    - Remington Typewriter Company (see Remington Rand, Inc.) (Box 81)
    - Remy, R., 1950-1954 (Box 81, Folder 3)
    - Rentschler, Mr. and Mrs. George A., 1938-1946 (Box 81, Folder 4)
    - Research Requests (see also Photograph Requests), 1966-1972 (Box 81, Folder 5)
    - Research Requests (see also Photograph Requests), 1973-1976 (Box 81, Folder 6)
    - Resch, Franz, 1960-1961 (Box 81, Folder 7)
    - Resor, Stanley, 1927-1946 (Box 81, Folder 8)
    - Revue de L'Art, 1970-1974 (Box 81, Folder 9)
    - Rewald, John, 1943-1978 (Box 81, Folder 10)
    - Reynolds, Andrew K., 1925 (Box 81, Folder 11)
    - Rheims, Maurice, 1946-1953 (Box 81, Folder 12)
    - Rheims, Maurice, 1954-1964 (Box 81, Folder 13)
    - Rheims, Maurice, 1965-1976 (Box 81, Folder 14)
    - Rhode, Mr. and Mrs. William, 1930-1935 (Box 81, Folder 15)
    - Ricci, Seymour de (see de Ricci, Seymour) (Box 81)
    - Rice, Mrs. Alexander Hamilton (Eleanor E.), 1923-1927 (Box 81, Folder 16)
    - Richard, Harold C., 1928-1929 (Box 81, Folder 17)
    - Richter, Mr. and Mrs. George M., 1932-1943 (Box 81, Folder 18)
    - Riddle, Mrs. John Wallace, 1937-1946 (Box 81, Folder 19)
    - Riezler, Kurt, 1941-1943 (Box 81, Folder 20)
    - Rinek, Charles Norvin, 1939-1941 (Box 81, Folder 21)
    - Ring, Grete, 1946-1951 (Box 81, Folder 22)
    - Ringling, Mr. and Mrs. John, 1924-1929 (Box 81, Folder 23)
    - Robbins, Horace, 1925-1926 (Box 81, Folder 24)
    - Robertson, Martha Barton, 1956-1962 (Box 81, Folder 25)
    - Robertson, Werring & Barto, Inc., 1926 (Box 81, Folder 26)
    - Robinson, Celia Sachs, 1936-1937 (Box 81, Folder 27)
    - Robinson, Edward G., 1935-1940 (Box 81, Folder 28)
    - Robinson, Edward G., 1941-1960 (Box 81, Folder 29)
    - Robinson, Gertrude Gheen (see Miss Gheen, Inc.) (Box 81)
    - Roche, Martine, 1967 (Box 81, Folder 30)
    - Rochelle, Mrs. R. C., 1947-1948 (Box 81, Folder 31)
    - Rochet, André, 1949 (Box 81, Folder 32)
    - Rockefeller, Godfrey S., 1940-1943 (Box 81, Folder 33)
    - Rockefeller, Mr. and Mrs. John D., Jr., 1924-1947 (Box 81, Folder 34)
    - Rockefeller, Nelson A., 1932-1950 (Box 81, Folder 35)
    - Roditi, Edouard and Violet, 1946-1947 (Box 81, Folder 36)
    - Roebling, Mrs. W. A., 1924-1927 (Box 81, Folder 37)
    - Roesler, Norbert L. H., 1969-1970 (Box 81, Folder 38)
    - Roger-Marx, Claude, 1954-1955 (Box 82, Folder 1)
    - Roger-Viollet, 1954-1965 (Box 82, Folder 2)
    - Rogers, Grace Rainey, 1924-1945 (Box 82, Folder 3)
    - Rogers, Mr. and Mrs. Henry H., 1911-1951 (Box 82, Folder 4)
    - Rogers, Mary Benjamin, 1929-1931 (Box 82, Folder 5)
    - Rogers, William A., 1925-1926 (Box 82, Folder 6)
    - Rohner, Gehrig & Co., Inc., 1951 (Box 82, Folder 7)
    - Rolick, Esther G., 1948-1956 (Box 82, Folder 8)
    - Romadka, Mary T., 1938-1939 (Box 82, Folder 9)
    - Romer, Charles, 1923-1924 (Box 82, Folder 10)
    - Roncin, Gustave, 1926-1932 (Box 82, Folder 11)
    - Roosevelt Recitals, 1927-1929 (Box 82, Folder 12)
    - Ropes, Mrs. Horace, 1925-1948 (Box 82, Folder 13)
    - Rorimer, James, 1925-1953 (Box 82, Folder 14)
    - Rose, Billy, 1940-1956 (Box 82, Folder 15)
    - Roselius, Ludwig, 1972 (Box 82, Folder 16)
    - Roseman, Charles, Jr., 1944-1951 (Box 82, Folder 17)
    - Rosen, Walter T., 1924-1936 (Box 82, Folder 18)
    - Rosenbach, A. W., 1929-1933 (Box 82, Folder 19)
    - Rosenbaum, Mrs. Joseph H., 1940-1943 (Box 82, Folder 20)
    - Rosenberg & Stiebel, 1949-1958 (Box 82, Folder 21)
    - Rosenberg, Paul, 1933-1946 (Box 82, Folder 22)
    - Rosenberg, Saemy, 1939 (Box 82, Folder 23)
    - Rosenbloom, Arthur, M., 1939-1944 (Box 82, Folder 24)
    - Rosenblum, Robert, 1969-1970 (Box 82, Folder 25)
    - Rosenfeld, Mr. and Mrs. Ernst, 1924-1937 (Box 82, Folder 26)
    - Rosenthal, A., 1960 (Box 82, Folder 27)
    - Rosenthal, Erwin, 1952-1956 (Box 82, Folder 28)
    - Rosenthal, Heinrich, 1953 (Box 82, Folder 29)
    - Rosenthal, Ludwig (name changed to Randall in 1942), 1937-1939 (Box 82, Folder 30)
    - Rosenthal, Mr. and Mrs. Moritz, 1929-1940 (Box 82, Folder 31)
    - Rosenthal, Paul and Ethel, 1935-1938 (Box 82, Folder 32)
    - Rosenwald, Mrs. Julius, 1925-1926 (Box 82, Folder 33)
    - Rosenwald, Lessing J., 1930-1953 (Box 82, Folder 34)
    - Rosenwald, Mr. and Mrs. Richard M., 1944-1948 (Box 82, Folder 35)
    - Ross, Mrs. Burke, 1925-1926 (Box 82, Folder 36)
    - Ross, Chandler, 1927-1929 (Box 82, Folder 37)
    - Ross, Denman, 1925-1931 (Box 82, Folder 38)
    - Rossbach, Mr. and Mrs. Harry, 1925-1926 (Box 82, Folder 39)
    - Rothenstein, John, 1942-1947 (Box 82, Folder 40)
    - Rothschild, Baroness Edouard de, 1952 (Box 82, Folder 41)
    - Rothschild, Baron and Baroness Eugène de, 1925-1941 (Box 82, Folder 42)
    - Rothschild, Baron Henri de, 1940-1945 (Box 82, Folder 43)
    - Rothschild, Herbert M., 1958 (Box 82, Folder 44)
    - Rothschild, Mr. and Mrs. Maurice, 1925-1952, 1976 (Box 82, Folder 45)
    - Rothschild, Max, 1929-1935 (Box 82, Folder 46)
    - Rothschild, Baron Robert de, 1941-1945 (Box 82, Folder 47)
    - Rothschild, Mr. and Mrs. Robert F., 1967-1974 (Box 82, Folder 48)
    - Rothschild, Mr. and Mrs. Walter N., 1927-1937 (Box 82, Folder 49)
    - Rottier, J. M., 1953 (Box 82, Folder 50)
    - Rougeron, M. J., 1925-1928 (Box 82, Folder 51)
    - Rouss, Mr. and Mrs. P. W., 1925-1926 (Box 82, Folder 52)
    - Rozet, Claude, 1976 (Box 82, Folder 53)
    - Rubin, Mr. and Mrs. J. Robert, 1935-1945 (Box 83, Folder 1)
    - Rudier, A., 1935-1949 (Box 83, Folder 2)
    - Rudolf Wendel, Inc., undated (Box 83, Folder 3)
    - Runes, Mary, 1937 (Box 83, Folder 4)
    - Ruppert, Jacob, 1925-1936 (Box 83, Folder 5)
    - Rushmore, Delight, 1934-1935 (Box 83, Folder 6)
    - Russell, Mrs. Charles H., Jr., 1932-1946 (Box 83, Folder 7)
    - Russell, Mrs. Henry P., 1933-1948 (Box 83, Folder 8)
    - Rust-Oppenheim, August, 1928-1938 (Box 83, Folder 9)
    - Ryan, Mrs. John B., 1949-1954 (Box 83, Folder 10)
    - Ryan, Mr. and Mrs. John D., 1925-1927 (Box 83, Folder 11)
    - Ryan, Thomas F., 1924-1932 (Box 83, Folder 12)
    - Ryback, Sonia, 1937-1938 (Box 83, Folder 13)
    - Ryerson, Mr. and Mrs. Joseph T., 1925-1949 (Box 83, Folder 14)
    - Ryle, Dorothy, 1937-1938 (Box 83, Folder 15)
    - Miscellaneous R: R-Ra, 1925-1977 (Box 83, Folder 16)
    - Miscellaneous R: Re, 1924-1976 (Box 83, Folder 17)
    - Miscellaneous R: Rh-Ric, 1923-1972 (Box 83, Folder 18)
    - Miscellaneous R: Rid-Riz, 1926-1976 (Box 83, Folder 19)
    - Miscellaneous R: Rob-Roc, 1924-1971 (Box 83, Folder 20)
    - Miscellaneous R: Rod-Ror, 1924-1975 (Box 83, Folder 21)
    - Miscellaneous R: Ros, 1924-1970 (Box 83, Folder 22)
    - Miscellaneous R: Rot-Roz, 1925-1970 (Box 83, Folder 23)
    - Miscellaneous R: Rub-Rum, 1923-1952 (Box 83, Folder 24)
    - Miscellaneous R: Run-Ry, 1925-1966 (Box 83, Folder 25)
    - Sabin, Frank T., 1926-1960 (Box 84, Folder 1)
    - Sabin, William, 1928-1935 (Box 84, Folder 2)
    - Sachs, Arthur, 1924-1929 (Box 84, Folder 3)
    - Sachs, Arthur, 1930-1941 (Box 84, Folder 4)
    - Sachs, Arthur, 1942 (Box 84, Folder 5)
    - Sachs, Arthur, 1943-1945 (Box 84, Folder 6)
    - Sachs, Arthur, 1946-1949 (Box 84, Folder 7)
    - Sachs, Arthur, 1949 (Box 84, Folder 8)
    - Sachs, Arthur, 1950 (Box 84, Folder 9)
    - Sachs, Arthur, 1951-1957 (Box 84, Folder 10)
    - Sachs, Edith, 1924-1942 (Box 84, Folder 11)
    - Sachs, Mr. and Mrs. Harry, 1923-1925 (Box 84, Folder 12)
    - Sachs, Mr. and Mrs. Harry, 1926-1937 (Box 84, Folder 13)
    - Sachs, Howard, 1925-1965 (Box 84, Folder 14)
    - Sachs, Maurice, 1931-1940 (Box 84, Folder 15)
    - Sachs, Paul J., 1929-1931 (Box 84, Folder 16)
    - Sacknoff, Mrs. Serge, 1943-1946 (Box 85, Folder 1)
    - Safron, Max, 1939-1952 (Box 85, Folder 2)
    - Saher, Mrs. Edward (Lilla) van (see van Saher, Mrs. Edward [Lilla]) (Box 85)
    - Sage, H. M., 1924-1929 (Box 85, Folder 3)
    - Sage-Quinton, Cornelia, 1926 (Box 85, Folder 4)
    - Saidenberg, Mrs. Daniel, 1948-1953 (Box 85, Folder 5)
    - Saisselin, Rémy, 1964-1971 (Box 85, Folder 6)
    - Saklatwalla, Mr. and Mrs. B. D., 1937-1945 (Box 85, Folder 7)
    - Salomon, Antoine, 1960-1964 (Box 85, Folder 8)
    - Salomon, Jacques, 1949 (Box 85, Folder 9)
    - Saltonstall, Mrs. R. M., 1938-1943 (Box 85, Folder 10)
    - Salz, Sam, 1938-1945 (Box 85, Folder 11)
    - Samuel H. Kress Foundation, 1924-1938 (Box 85, Folder 12)
    - Samuel H. Kress Foundation, 1939-1950 (Box 85, Folder 13)
    - Samuel H. Kress Foundation, 1951-1953 (Box 85, Folder 14)
    - Samuel H. Kress Foundation, 1954-1977 (Box 85, Folder 15)
    - Samuel T. Freeman & Co., 1943-1963 (Box 85, Folder 16)
    - Sanchez Canton, F., 1934-1935 (Box 85, Folder 17)
    - Sandblom, Philip, 1938-1959 (Box 85, Folder 18)
    - Sandoz, Marc, 1957-1960 (Box 85, Folder 19)
    - Sandoz, Marc, 1961 (Box 85, Folder 20)
    - Sandoz, Marc, 1962 (Box 85, Folder 21)
    - Sandoz, Marc, 1963 (Box 85, Folder 22)
    - Sandoz, Marc, 1964 (Box 85, Folder 23)
    - Sandoz, Marc, 1965-1966 (Box 85, Folder 24)
    - Sandoz, Marc, 1967-1974 (Box 85, Folder 25)
    - Sandoz, Maurice, 1941-1942 (Box 85, Folder 26)
    - Sanes, Samuel, 1946 (Box 86, Folder 1)
    - Sansoni Publishers, 1953 (Box 86, Folder 2)
    - Sarnoff, David, 1935-1943 (Box 86, Folder 3)
    - Sassoon, Philip, 1932-1933 (Box 86, Folder 4)
    - Satterwhite, Dr. Preston Pope, 1925-1942 (Box 86, Folder 5)
    - Saturday Review, 1951-1958 (Box 86, Folder 6)
    - Scarlett, Rolph, 1943-1950 (Box 86, Folder 7)
    - Schaeffer Galleries, Inc., 1936-1967 (Box 86, Folder 8)
    - Schapiro, Meyer, 1938-1975 (Box 86, Folder 9)
    - Schauensee, Baron de and Baroness Rudolphe (see de Schauensee, Baron and Baroness Rudolphe) (Box 86)
    - Schempp, Theodore, 1934-1945 (Box 86, Folder 10)
    - Schempp, Theodore, 1924-1947 (Box 86, Folder 11)
    - Schempp, Theodore, 1948-1954 (Box 86, Folder 12)
    - Scherbatoff, Georges, 1932 (Box 86, Folder 13)
    - Schierstedt, Lucy von (see von Schierstedt, Lucy) (Box 86)
    - Schiff, John M., 1935-1938 (Box 86, Folder 14)
    - Schiff, John M., 1939 (Box 86, Folder 15)
    - Schiff, John M., 1940-1947 (Box 86, Folder 16)
    - Schiff, John M., 1948-1974 (Box 86, Folder 17)
    - Schiff, Mortimer L., 1925-1935 (Box 86, Folder 18)
    - Schiffer, Jack W., 1925-1926 (Box 86, Folder 19)
    - Schil, Bernard, Claude, & Gilbert, 1964-1978 (Box 86, Folder 20)
    - Schilling, Edmund, 1956-1969 (Box 86, Folder 21)
    - Schimmel, Norbert, 1957-1959 (Box 86, Folder 22)
    - Schinasi, Leon, 1925-1935 (Box 86, Folder 23)
    - Schlee, George M., 1942 (Box 86, Folder 24)
    - Schlenoff, Norman, 1965-1969 (Box 86, Folder 25)
    - Schmitz-Hille, Peter, 1970-1973 (Box 86, Folder 26)
    - Schnapper, Antoine, 1965-1968 (Box 86, Folder 27)
    - Schniewind, Henry, Jr., 1925-1936 (Box 86, Folder 28)
    - Schoeller, André, 1934-1947 (Box 86, Folder 29)
    - Schofield, Frank and Flora, 1938-1948 (Box 86, Folder 30)
    - Schöne, Dr. Wolfgang, 1958-1959 (Box 86, Folder 31)
    - Schuette, Mrs. Robert W., 1924-1943 (Box 86, Folder 32)
    - Schulte, Mr. and Mrs. D. A, 1925-1929 (Box 87, Folder 1)
    - Schulthess, Hans de (see de Schulthess, Hans) (Box 87)
    - Schumacher, A., 1948-1949 (Box 87, Folder 2)
    - Schumacher, Frederick W., 1943-1946 (Box 87, Folder 3)
    - Schwab, Charles M., 1923-1942 (Box 87, Folder 4)
    - Schwartz, Max H., 1930-1933 (Box 87, Folder 5)
    - Sciolette, Maximo, 1952-1953 (Box 87, Folder 6)
    - Sciolette, Maximo, 1954-1967 (Box 87, Folder 7)
    - Scott, Maj. Alfred I., 1941 (Box 87, Folder 8)
    - Scott & Fowles, 1925-1947 (Box 87, Folder 9)
    - Scott, Edgar, 1937-1945 (Box 87, Folder 10)
    - Scott, Rufus W., 1929-1938 (Box 87, Folder 11)
    - Scribner's Magazine, 1924-1927 (Box 87, Folder 12)
    - Searle, Mrs. John, 1939-1945 (Box 87, Folder 13)
    - Seasongood, Murray, 1930-1945 (Box 87, Folder 14)
    - Secor, Arthur J., 1927-1934 (Box 87, Folder 15)
    - Secrest, Meryle (see Beveridge, Meryle Secrest) (Box 87)
    - Segesser von Brunegg, F., 1960-1961 (Box 87, Folder 16)
    - Segni, Leopoldo di (see di Segni, Leopoldo) (Box 87)
    - Seidman, Mrs. Herbert A., 1970 (Box 87, Folder 17)
    - Seilern, Count Antoine, 1951-1955 (Box 87, Folder 18)
    - Seligman, Mr. and Mrs. James, 1925-1959 (Box 87, Folder 19)
    - Seligmann & Cie., S.A. (Geneva) (see G. Seligmann & Cie., S.A. Geneva) (Box 87)
    - Seligmann & Cie. (Paris), 1941-1946 (Box 87, Folder 20)
    - Seligmann & Cie. (Paris), 1947 (Box 87, Folder 21)
    - Seligmann & Cie. (Paris), 1948 (Box 87, Folder 22)
    - Seligmann & Cie. (Paris), 1949 (Box 87, Folder 23)
    - Seligmann & Cie. (Paris), 1950 (Box 87, Folder 24)
    - Seligmann & Cie. (Paris), 1951-1953 (Box 87, Folder 25)
    - Seligmann, André, 1940-1947 (Box 87, Folder 26)
    - Seligmann, André, 1945 (Box 87, Folder 27)
      (papers relating to his death)
    - Seligmann, François-Gerard, 1953-1962 (Box 88, Folder 1)
    - Seligmann, François-Gerard, 1963-1967 (Box 88, Folder 2)
    - Seligmann, François-Gerard, 1968-1976 (Box 88, Folder 3)
    - Seligmann, Georges E., 1936-1949 (Box 88, Folder 4)
    - Seligmann, Georges E., 1949-1951 (Box 88, Folder 5)
    - Seligmann, Jaqueline, 1929-1951 (Box 88, Folder 6)
    - Seligmann, Paris Building, 1935 (Box 88, Folder 7)
    - Seligmann, Paris Building, 1935-1936 (Box 88, Folder 8)
    - Seligmann, René, 1924-1929 (Box 88, Folder 9)
      (records of routine personal transactions and financial papers)
    - Selznick, Mrs. David O., 1941-1945 (Box 88, Folder 10)
    - Semon Bache & Co., 1926-1929 (Box 88, Folder 11)
    - Semple, Mr. and Mrs. William T., 1930-1944 (Box 88, Folder 12)
    - Sesquicentennial International Exposition, 1926 (Box 88, Folder 13)
    - Severance, John L., 1923-1929 (Box 88, Folder 14)
    - Seward, C. A., 1934-1935 (Box 88, Folder 15)
    - Seyburn, Mrs. Wesson, 1925-1938 (Box 88, Folder 16)
    - Shannon, Charles E., 1938-1940 (Box 89, Folder 1)
    - Shapiro, Morris, 1941-1949 (Box 89, Folder 2)
    - Sharpe, Mrs. Henry D., 1931-1949 (Box 89, Folder 3)
    - Sheffield, James R., 1925-1936 (Box 89, Folder 4)
    - Shelden, Mrs. Allan, 1936-1945 (Box 89, Folder 5)
    - Sheldon, Marshall, 1934-1938 (Box 89, Folder 6)
    - Sheon, Aaron, 1970-1973 (Box 89, Folder 7)
    - Sherfesse, Forsythe, 1937-1939 (Box 89, Folder 8)
    - Sherman, Frederic Fairchild, 1923-1932 (Box 89, Folder 9)
    - Sherman, Irving H., 1939-1973 (Box 89, Folder 10)
    - Sherry, Louis, 1929-1930 (Box 89, Folder 11)
    - Shillard-Smith, Mrs. C., 1936-1938 (Box 89, Folder 12)
    - Shirley, Andrew, 1952 (Box 89, Folder 13)
    - Shoenberg, Sydney M., 1936-1938 (Box 89, Folder 14)
    - Sickles, Daniel, 1936-1941 (Box 89, Folder 15)
    - Sidley, Irene, 1923-1938 (Box 89, Folder 16)
    - Sidley, Mrs. John Streeter, 1925-1936 (Box 89, Folder 17)
    - Sieff, Israel M., 1935-1952 (Box 89, Folder 18)
    - Silberberg, Daniel H., 1934-1935 (Box 89, Folder 19)
    - Simmons, Percy, 1967-1970 (Box 89, Folder 20)
    - Simon, Otto M., 1944-1945 (Box 89, Folder 21)
    - Simonds, Mrs. W. R., 1928-1929 (Box 89, Folder 22)
    - Simonson, Lee, 1934-1939 (Box 89, Folder 23)
    - Simpson, Jean W., 1942-1943 (Box 89, Folder 24)
    - Simpson, Mrs. John W., 1924-1942 (Box 89, Folder 25)
    - Singleton, Esther, 1925-1928 (Box 89, Folder 26)
    - Sinkler, Mr. and Mrs. James M. R., 1948 (Box 89, Folder 27)
    - Sinkler, Mrs. Wharton, 1925-1948 (Box 89, Folder 28)
    - Skinner, William, II, 1930 (Box 89, Folder 29)
    - Skira, Inc., Publishers, 1954-1961 (Box 89, Folder 30)
    - Sloan, Mrs. Alfred P., 1924-1943 (Box 89, Folder 31)
    - Sloog, Maurice, 1923-1950 (Box 89, Folder 32)
    - Smail, Zita Yvonne, 1936-1937 (Box 89, Folder 33)
    - Small, Mrs. Arthur, 1934 (Box 89, Folder 34)
    - Smith, Frank C., Jr., 1934-1940 (Box 89, Folder 35)
    - Smith, Gertrude Robinson, 1947-1948 (Box 89, Folder 36)
    - Smith, Mr. and Mrs. John Thomas, 1927-1941 (Box 89, Folder 37)
    - Smith, Lawrence H., 1930-1932 (Box 90, Folder 1)
    - Smith, Lotus Robb, 1929-1933 (Box 90, Folder 2)
    - Snyder, Mrs. Henry S., 1925-1936 (Box 90, Folder 3)
    - Soby, James T., 1933-1956 (Box 90, Folder 4)
    - Société de l'Histoire de l'Art Français, 1968-1972 (Box 90, Folder 5)
    - Société des Amis du Louvre, 1973-1977 (Box 90, Folder 6)
    - Société Française d'Archéologie, 1964-1975 (Box 90, Folder 7)
    - Société Française de Bienfaisance, 1923-1930 (Box 90, Folder 8)
    - Society of Arts and Crafts, 1924-1935 (Box 90, Folder 9)
    - Soegaard, L. P., 1949-1950 (Box 90, Folder 10)
    - Soifer, Nathaniel, 1961-1970 (Box 90, Folder 11)
    - Solberg, Marshall, 1932 (Box 90, Folder 12)
    - Soldatenkof, Mme. A., 1929 (Box 90, Folder 13)
    - Solicitations (primarily from charities), 1943-1952 (Box 90, Folder 14)
    - Solomon, Arthur K., 1953-1973 (Box 90, Folder 15)
    - Solomon R. Guggenheim Foundation, 1937-1953 (Box 90, Folder 16)
    - Somers, Harold, 1924-1925 (Box 90, Folder 17)
    - Sonnenberg, Benjamin, 1957-1973 (Box 90, Folder 18)
    - Sonnino, Gabriel, 1950 (Box 90, Folder 19)
    - Sotheby & Co., 1937-1959 (Box 90, Folder 20)
    - Sotheby & Co., 1960-1975 (Box 90, Folder 21)
    - Southam, H. S., 1937-1938 (Box 90, Folder 22)
    - Southworth Press, 1934 (Box 90, Folder 23)
    - Souza, Roberto Pinto De (see De Souza, Roberto Pinto) (Box 90)
    - Soyer, Charles, 1950-1952 (Box 90, Folder 24)
    - Spaeth, Mr. and Mrs. Otto Lucien, 1945-1955 (Box 91, Folder 1)
    - Spaulding, Mr. and Mrs. Harry B., 1933-1943 (Box 91, Folder 2)
    - Spaulding, John T., 1925-1943 (Box 91, Folder 3)
    - Speelman, Edward, 1955-1968 (Box 91, Folder 4)
    - Speiser, Mr. and Mrs. Maurice J., 1932-1948 (Box 91, Folder 5)
    - Sperber, Lionel A., 1936-1937 (Box 91, Folder 6)
    - Spero, Arthur, 1928-1930 (Box 91, Folder 7)
    - Speyer, Mr. and Mrs. Edgar, 1929-1934 (Box 91, Folder 8)
    - Spingarn, Clifford, 1973-1976 (Box 91, Folder 9)
    - Spingold, Nathan B., 1939-1949 (Box 91, Folder 10)
    - Spink & Son, Ltd., 1928-1947 (Box 91, Folder 11)
    - Spink, C. Marshall, 1949-1961 (Box 91, Folder 12)
    - Spink, Jack (see Spink & Son, Ltd.) (Box 91)
    - Spinola, Ugo Pietro, 1923-1924 (Box 91, Folder 13)
    - Spiro, Stephen B., 1968-1969 (Box 91, Folder 14)
    - Sprague, Frederick L., 1948-1949 (Box 91, Folder 15)
    - Spreckels, Mrs. Adolph, 1925-1947 (Box 91, Folder 16)
    - Sprong, Heléne, 1938-1939 (Box 91, Folder 17)
    - Spur, 1921-1938 (Box 91, Folder 18)
    - Squier, C. B., 1924-1927 (Box 91, Folder 19)
    - Stadt Schaffhausen, 1947 (Box 91, Folder 20)
    - Stair and Andrew, Inc., 1936 (Box 91, Folder 21)
    - Standard & Poor's Corporation, 1953-1961 (Box 91, Folder 22)
    - Stang, J. B., 1929-1947 (Box 91, Folder 23)
    - State of New York, 1927-1940 (Box 91, Folder 24)
    - Staub, John, 1934-1939 (Box 91, Folder 25)
    - Stauffer, Thomas B., 1947-1948 (Box 91, Folder 26)
    - Steegmuller, Francis, 1946-1956 (Box 91, Folder 27)
    - Steen, Carla, 1955-1962 (Box 91, Folder 28)
    - Stegmann, Rechtsanwalt (see also Thurn & Taxis-Metternich, Princess), 1924-1935 (Box 91, Folder 29)
    - Stehli, Mr. and Mrs. Emil, 1927-1942 (Box 91, Folder 30)